let questions = [
    {
        numb: 0,
        question: "Ready to take the quiz again?",
        answer: "YES, I AM READY!",
        options: [
            "YES, I AM READY!",
            "NO",
            "yes",
            "no :("
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What quantum number describes the size and energy of the orbital and relative distance from the nucleus?",
        answer: "A) principal quantum number (n)",
        options: [
            "A) principal quantum number (n)",
            "B) angular momentum quantum number (l)",
            "C) magnetic quantum number (ml)",
            "D) spin quantum number (ms)" 
        ]
    },
{
    numb: 2,
    question: "What quantum number indicates the direction the electron is spinning?",
    answer: "D) spin quantum number (ms)",
    options: [
        "A) principal quantum number (n)",
        "B) angular momentum quantum number (l)",
        "C) magnetic quantum number (ml)",
        "D) spin quantum number (ms)" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 3,
    question: "What quantum number describes the orientation of the orbital sound around the nucleus?",
    answer: "C) magnetic quantum number (ml)",
    options: [
        "A) principal quantum number (n)",
        "B) angular momentum quantum number (l)",
        "C) magnetic quantum number (ml)",
        "D) spin quantum number (ms)" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 4,
    question: "What quantum number describes the shape of the orbitals?",
    answer: "D) angular momentum quantum number (l)",
    options: [
        "A) principal quantum number (n)",
        "B) magnetic quantum number (ml)",
        "C) spin quantum number (ms)",
        "D) angular momentum quantum number (l)" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 5,
    question: "A fault on which the two blocks slide past one What principle states that no two electrons in an atom can have the same set of the four quantum numbers?",
    answer: "B) Pauli’s Exclusion Principle",
    options: [
        "A) Aufbau Principle",
        "B) Pauli’s Exclusion Principle",
        "C) Electron Configuration Principle",
        "D) Bohr Principle" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 6,
    question: "What principle describes the order in which the electrons enter the different orbitals and sublevels?",
    answer: "A) Aufbau Principle",
    options: [
        "A) Aufbau Principle",
        "B) Electron Configuration Principle",
        "C) Pauli’s Exclusion Principle",
        "D) Bohr Principle" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the electron configuration of Lithium (3 electrons)?",
    answer: "C) 1s²2s¹",
    options: [
        "A) 1s¹2s¹2p¹",
        "B) 1s³",
        "C) 1s²2s¹",
        "D) 1s²2s²" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the use of the n and l quantum numbers along with the number of electrons?",
    answer: "B) electron configuration",
    options: [
        "A) quantum number",
        "B) electron configuration",
        "C) Bohr model",
        "D) box diagram" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 9,
    question: "How many electrons can a s-subshell hold?",
    answer: "A) 2",
    options: [
        "A) 2",
        "B) 3",
        "C) 1",
        "D) 0" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 10,
    question: "How many electrons can a d-subshell hold?",
    answer: "D) 10",
    options: [
        "A) 0",
        "B) 5",
        "C) 14",
        "D) 10", 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 11,
    question: "What orbital has a spherical shape with the nucleus at the center of the sphere?",
    answer: "C) s-orbital",
    options: [
        "A) p-orbital",
        "B) d-orbital",
        "C) s-orbital",
        "D) f-orbital" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 12,
    question: "What orbital has a more complex shape?",
    answer: "B) f-orbital",
    options: [
        "A) s-orbital",
        "B) f-orbital",
        "C) d-orbital",
        "D) p-orbital" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 13,
    question: "What does the Pauli Exclusion Principle state?",
    answer: "A) Two electrons in the same atom cannot have the same set of quantum numbers",
    options: [
        "A) Two electrons in the same atom cannot have the same set of quantum numbers",
        "B) Electrons repel each other",
        "C) Electrons attract protons",
        "D) Electrons move in elliptical orbits" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which subshell corresponds to the quantum numbers l=2?",
    answer: "D) d",
    options: [
        "A) p",
        "B) s",
        "C) f",
        "D) d" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 15,
    question: "In the quantum mechanical model, what does the spin quantum number (ms) describe?",
    answer: "B) The direction the electron is spinning",
    options: [
        "A) The orientation of the orbital",
        "B) The direction the electron is spinning",
        "C) The shape of the orbital",
        "D) strike-slip faultThe energy level of the electron"
    ]
}
];
